

PERSONAL

Birthday : 11 April 1994
Nationality : Greek & South African

Languages : English

SKILLS

HTMI **UX DESIGN** CSS **UI DESIGN BOOTSTRAP** WIRE-FRAMING **JAVASCRIPT PROTOTYPING JQUERY USER RESEARCH** REACT MOCK UPS MONGODR **GRAPHIC DESIGN EXPRESS PHOTOGRAPHY**

IMAGE EDITING

SOFTWARE

NODEJS

VS CODE PHOTOSHOP
BOOTSTRAP STUDIO LIGHTROOM
WORDPRESS ILLUSTRATOR
MS OFFICE ADOBE XD

SOFT SKILLS

CRITICAL THINKING HONESTY

COMMUNICATION AUTHENTICITY

FAST LEARNING TIME MANAGEMENT

HUMOUR RELIABILITY

CONTACT



Cape Town, South Africa



+27 84 413 5465



nikitabatlis@live.com



https://nikitabatlis.github.io/portfolio/

NIKITA BATLIS

Web Developer

PROFILE

After spending many years working abroad, I returned home to continue my education and a forge a career in Web Development and UX/UI design.

Having completed my bootcamp and diploma, I am looking for an entry-level/junior position or internship within a strong team to further my industry knowledge.

I thrive on creative front-end challenges and enjoy implementing UI trends into my current projects. I have a particular interest in inclusive and accessible UX design and believe the key to a product's longterm success is putting the user's experience first.

Equipped with a conscientious work ethic - I am a reliable, proactive colleague with a keen eye for detail, and will never skip an opportunity to learn something from someone new.

EDUCATION

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP

HYPERIONDEV, CAPE TOWN

A three month intensive bootcamp covering the MERN stack and other basic Web Dev fundamentals. 2020

BRAND & MARKETING MANAGEMENT

VEGA SCHOOL OF BRAND LEADERSHIP
Part time course to develop
both theoretical and practical knowledge in the
field of brand building and marketing.
2019

PROFESSIONAL DIPLOMA IN UX DESIGN

UX DESIGN INSTITUTE, IRELAND
Correspondence course in professional
UX design user theory, research methods
and prototyping work-flows.
2019 - 2020

DIGITAL MARKETING & GRAPHIC DESIGN

THE UNIVERSITY OF CAPE TOWN

Correspondence certification via the GetSmarter platform - covering the fundamentals and current trends in digital marketing and graphic design. 2019

JOB HISTORY

Photographer & Worpress Designer

Apr 2019 - Present

Freelance | Cape Town

Commissioned in fine art beauty, portraiture and real estate photography. As well as specialized Squarespace or Wordpress website designs for small local businesses.

Location Scout & Researcher

Nov 2018 - Mar 2019

Cape Town Productions | www.ctprod.co.za | $Cape\ Town$

A summer contract managing and updating the company's location database while researching and scouting new locations around Cape Town. Along with assisting on set and in-office coordinators.

Stewardess

Dec 2017 - Sep 2018

Katara | 123m Private Motor Yacht | *Spain* Working & living closely with a team of 70 multinationals. Managing & maintaining luxury yacht interiors while delivering 10 Star service for Arab Royalty.

Junior Stewardess

Apr 2017 - Sep 2017

Lady Nag Nag | 53m Motor Yacht | France & Monaco

Seasonal contract on board a demanding, fast pased privately owned yacht.

REFERENCES

Gavin Hartford Stakeholder Solutions +27 82 903 1725 gavin@stakeholdersolutions.co.za Gabi Lowe Upfront Marketing & The Coaching Nest +27 83 455 4774 gabi@thecoachingnest.co.za